<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Programming on James MacPherson</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/tags/programming/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Programming on James MacPherson</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 03 Mar 2025 11:41:22 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/tags/programming/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Day Four</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/day-four/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Mar 2025 11:41:22 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/day-four/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Mood: Optimistic&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;After only waking 3 times last night I am, for the first time in a long time, actually feeling somewhat rested!  I had to listen to my stories to first drift off to sleep because I couldn&amp;rsquo;t stop myself daydreaming about &amp;lsquo;The Detective&amp;rsquo; but once I actually got myself down I didn&amp;rsquo;t need to use them again.  Other than that I think I&amp;rsquo;m actually starting to feel my medication start to take effect. I&amp;rsquo;m much less focused on my own demise and have even had a few thoughts of the future - something I didn&amp;rsquo;t expect quite so soon.&#xA;Maybe this will actually work for me&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>First Post</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/first-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2025 11:41:49 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/first-post/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Mood:  Meh / Average&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Yesterday I contacted my GP and restarted antidepressants.  To be clear I&amp;rsquo;m doing this solely to fulfil a promise - not because I expect any improvement. I promised that I&amp;rsquo;d make a real effort to recover so I&amp;rsquo;m on the drug that several US studies show is best for my particular circumstances.  This blog will serve as a record for me to look back on so that I can, at the very least, look back and accurately evaluate any progress I might make towartds stable mental health.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
